You can't outrun family
Rogue River is a horror, thriller film directed by Jourdan McClure.
When a young woman takes a trip down Rogue River,
her car mysteriously disappears.
Lost without transport or communication, she accepts the hospitality of a
stranger who offers her shelter for the night at his cabin.
With no other options available, she reluctantly
accepts only to forever regret it.
The ensuing hours yield nothing but torture,
indescribable pain, and horrific agony.
If you've seen Misery, you've seen nothing.
This movie starts where horror films end and leaves
viewers paralysed by fear and disgust.
Mara, played by Michelle Page.
Peter, played by Art Alexakis.
Andrew, played by Chris Coy.
Sherrif Boyd, played by Michael Cudlitz.
Lea, played by Lucinda Jenney.
Jon, played by Bill Moseley.
Rogue River is a 1951 American Western film directed by John Rawlins
and starring Rory Calhoun, Peter Graves, Frank Fenton.
The film was made in Cinecolor, a cheaper alternative to Technicolor.
Location shooting took place at Grants Pass in Oregon.
The tone is dark and intense.